{"72ac48d9-492f-4b5d-a971-febd36e95e58":{"text":"Athens","question":"1738e5db-453a-4cce-84ed-cb0394ca3310","isCorrect":true},"304bf76b-bcf5-4c42-ac57-2b5c19a94f46":{"text":"Rome","question":"1738e5db-453a-4cce-84ed-cb0394ca3310","isCorrect":false},"f8fbc995-0321-4276-a308-d778849582f1":{"text":"London","question":"1738e5db-453a-4cce-84ed-cb0394ca3310","isCorrect":false},"9f801386-6008-47f6-9fc3-6133722aad44":{"text":"Paris","question":"1738e5db-453a-4cce-84ed-cb0394ca3310","isCorrect":false},"b3381aa8-9f74-4a64-b870-ab8422e9681b":{"text":"Manchester United","question":"312ba3b2-be56-442a-bddb-c2cb38f1d12d","isCorrect":true},"8d776300-7706-4c6b-93d5-fdaeff973729":{"text":"Liverpool F.C","question":"312ba3b2-be56-442a-bddb-c2cb38f1d12d","isCorrect":false},"ec4613bb-e87f-469e-95b6-8edda2f8e56c":{"text":"Chelsea F.C","question":"312ba3b2-be56-442a-bddb-c2cb38f1d12d","isCorrect":false},"4caa4b05-3723-4a44-9ca5-5221634c303b":{"text":"Bayern Munchen F.C","question":"312ba3b2-be56-442a-bddb-c2cb38f1d12d","isCorrect":false},"b38a2082-d4c1-4df6-bc8f-88ebe4002bf3":{"text":"Serena Williams","question":"002aee64-a06f-4cc0-a5a5-2dd7e19d81aa","isCorrect":true},"3a87126a-099a-4ef4-9a65-7f961135249b":{"text":"Selena Gomez","question":"002aee64-a06f-4cc0-a5a5-2dd7e19d81aa","isCorrect":false},"fd67639a-ce00-449b-a7ed-5ea46404f102":{"text":"Margaret Court","question":"002aee64-a06f-4cc0-a5a5-2dd7e19d81aa","isCorrect":false},"f98fa458-6d49-49e6-a9a7-f5e4e1bcc8a7":{"text":"Maria Sharapova","question":"002aee64-a06f-4cc0-a5a5-2dd7e19d81aa","isCorrect":false},"b5b824bb-47e1-4ba1-97db-bba332f52812":{"text":"Michael Schumacher","question":"4c1b66c3-6144-4843-b2d5-479b05010f32","isCorrect":true},"ea63d016-afc5-4bc1-9322-5fd8148b5700":{"text":"Esteban Ocon","question":"4c1b66c3-6144-4843-b2d5-479b05010f32","isCorrect":false},"9a8a352a-e14b-4953-b378-563ef956115f":{"text":"George Russell","question":"4c1b66c3-6144-4843-b2d5-479b05010f32","isCorrect":false},"23d1dd1a-36fa-4f34-8797-1e1285f4b4fc":{"text":"Kevin Magnusse","question":"4c1b66c3-6144-4843-b2d5-479b05010f32","isCorrect":false},"283853a5-7e98-4f9d-9e70-badd2f7d4bb5":{"text":"Blue Ribbon Sports","question":"92ab575e-ea7c-4183-8cf8-1666892c7d21","isCorrect":true},"388b7c0f-0817-4205-a297-3eb7499f61b3":{"text":"Diamont Sports","question":"92ab575e-ea7c-4183-8cf8-1666892c7d21","isCorrect":false},"6c8395c1-b2cf-4ee1-8751-d4818ea9f400":{"text":"Fenix Sports","question":"92ab575e-ea7c-4183-8cf8-1666892c7d21","isCorrect":false},"74da4643-8908-43e3-9583-8be348ab2804":{"text":"Nikels Sports","question":"92ab575e-ea7c-4183-8cf8-1666892c7d21","isCorrect":false},"ee8702ff-3876-426d-b540-94178bc68bf2":{"text":"1997","question":"17d9cccb-7db0-4b48-aad5-9f5404cdc54a","isCorrect":true},"5b9d28a7-4ce7-4f09-aead-8bb95c8532ff":{"text":"1996","question":"17d9cccb-7db0-4b48-aad5-9f5404cdc54a","isCorrect":false},"f35dfd89-0501-4ab7-9652-c0b93be7b6d1":{"text":"1995","question":"17d9cccb-7db0-4b48-aad5-9f5404cdc54a","isCorrect":false},"24814a34-03aa-4ccb-80b7-6143115ff60c":{"text":"2000","question":"17d9cccb-7db0-4b48-aad5-9f5404cdc54a","isCorrect":false},"235be84d-7e8b-4911-ba0f-92f9f5772990":{"text":"Stranger Things","question":"2e676032-e8e1-4947-a2ca-fab3450006a3","isCorrect":true},"ba0f3189-4921-4b99-b087-aebce518a483":{"text":"Money Heist","question":"2e676032-e8e1-4947-a2ca-fab3450006a3","isCorrect":false},"938e5a20-5539-4a3c-a1f4-234c257e2888":{"text":"Game of thrones","question":"2e676032-e8e1-4947-a2ca-fab3450006a3","isCorrect":false},"2092ec16-71b2-4c3d-b60e-6fe1e1bd31d3":{"text":"The Walking dead","question":"2e676032-e8e1-4947-a2ca-fab3450006a3","isCorrect":false},"03cb6ceb-bbba-42c5-b1c9-40dbef0f9963":{"text":"Snow White","question":"2ac83bb7-eaee-422b-a418-1cb15bd45840","isCorrect":true},"d230966a-5a2b-4da6-bd95-e9912bec94e1":{"text":"Pinocchio","question":"2ac83bb7-eaee-422b-a418-1cb15bd45840","isCorrect":false},"b64b386b-46e7-4437-835b-04e84107c05e":{"text":"Fancy","question":"2ac83bb7-eaee-422b-a418-1cb15bd45840","isCorrect":false},"36c0466d-8428-45e7-a9fd-c6561c93b5e4":{"text":"Dumbo","question":"2ac83bb7-eaee-422b-a418-1cb15bd45840","isCorrect":false},"a4ea5e9b-2314-4730-9b59-e7c8cd654206":{"text":"Central Perk","question":"90680995-38cd-4c7d-861a-c69402852035","isCorrect":true},"59e59fee-bcd7-499e-ac6c-da15fdf6984b":{"text":"Kimera","question":"90680995-38cd-4c7d-861a-c69402852035","isCorrect":false},"bbfd908d-669b-44b7-ac9b-dcf98fc61401":{"text":"Monkeys Cofee","question":"90680995-38cd-4c7d-861a-c69402852035","isCorrect":false},"1cd0f9ff-0d5e-4acf-a76c-fb1d8bd92fdc":{"text":"Jet coffee","question":"90680995-38cd-4c7d-861a-c69402852035","isCorrect":false},"f75260be-eccf-474d-99c8-ee9ae43a499a":{"text":"Toy Story","question":"0d45cce7-7193-4324-b284-c4a73dfa4b0b","isCorrect":true},"86972610-f826-4fc4-8438-7e8054d0a6cf":{"text":"Monsters","question":"0d45cce7-7193-4324-b284-c4a73dfa4b0b","isCorrect":false},"58819af0-ef9b-49a6-8204-57054e6acdaa":{"text":"A Bugs Life","question":"0d45cce7-7193-4324-b284-c4a73dfa4b0b","isCorrect":false},"0c253f89-a9fc-4954-b8a4-739ef6a20fd1":{"text":"Cars","question":"0d45cce7-7193-4324-b284-c4a73dfa4b0b","isCorrect":false},"78a567ad-d66d-4c11-a29b-33d5aa53c8c3":{"text":"The Angels","question":"a745a1c3-1506-4004-a5e9-ef8db6f2d3ca","isCorrect":true},"47db476b-a96c-46a0-af11-22e6344fd25f":{"text":"Miami","question":"a745a1c3-1506-4004-a5e9-ef8db6f2d3ca","isCorrect":false},"e22afdee-51a0-4bb1-bf76-8dee8a32843c":{"text":"New York","question":"a745a1c3-1506-4004-a5e9-ef8db6f2d3ca","isCorrect":false},"66cdd187-8814-4f67-bae3-7f9219440eeb":{"text":"Albuquerque","question":"a745a1c3-1506-4004-a5e9-ef8db6f2d3ca","isCorrect":false},"bb115ced-d3ba-421e-9aa9-8e4ba7b2e4b0":{"text":"Liverpool","question":"4ed7818c-6c69-42e8-887d-2948c21faa72","isCorrect":true},"2df74959-411a-4df1-af9b-7047f3f83574":{"text":"London","question":"4ed7818c-6c69-42e8-887d-2948c21faa72","isCorrect":false},"717f4375-da69-4bec-96af-b4aebfe1a2fc":{"text":"Leeds","question":"4ed7818c-6c69-42e8-887d-2948c21faa72","isCorrect":false},"30f7fb2a-09bd-4036-8746-34445aaa5eec":{"text":"Birmingham","question":"4ed7818c-6c69-42e8-887d-2948c21faa72","isCorrect":false},"88e6cd0c-3b95-43f6-aac0-12c22434efb2":{"text":"Ed Sheeran, The Shape of You","question":"5ead65df-33ed-4b30-8e87-db071c181912","isCorrect":true},"388ad9a1-3db5-4e48-ade3-d355880702e0":{"text":"Bad Guy, Billie Eilish","question":"5ead65df-33ed-4b30-8e87-db071c181912","isCorrect":false},"99af2da7-04de-4ee4-a244-85e8759127ce":{"text":"Sunflower, Post Malone & Swae Lee","question":"5ead65df-33ed-4b30-8e87-db071c181912","isCorrect":false},"9eea97c9-73ba-40d7-9fd8-2c59e37543cc":{"text":"Dance Monkey, Tones and I","question":"5ead65df-33ed-4b30-8e87-db071c181912","isCorrect":false},"163fe90c-b16b-40ec-9b88-9ed277ecb079":{"text":"Maroon 5","question":"b4d6e592-9781-48c3-a467-7a9262889fd4","isCorrect":true},"9b3fa1b3-ad91-430a-86ab-5f98d7262890":{"text":"Gorillaz","question":"b4d6e592-9781-48c3-a467-7a9262889fd4","isCorrect":false},"1ec13e7b-58d2-4205-a514-67113b98bcea":{"text":"Linkin Park","question":"b4d6e592-9781-48c3-a467-7a9262889fd4","isCorrect":false},"28891631-f3a1-44a5-9e27-176117fba259":{"text":"The Green Day","question":"b4d6e592-9781-48c3-a467-7a9262889fd4","isCorrect":false},"6ecd6e3c-6e1e-445e-90b1-d3a15068f13e":{"text":"88","question":"f91d440a-c9c9-48af-ad83-cd0313d6dcac","isCorrect":true},"c5ff2182-1b16-49d4-9533-f2102bb27e73":{"text":"92","question":"f91d440a-c9c9-48af-ad83-cd0313d6dcac","isCorrect":false},"42f8daf6-67c3-456f-8506-7b831eecb263":{"text":"81","question":"f91d440a-c9c9-48af-ad83-cd0313d6dcac","isCorrect":false},"d3d63cf8-47f3-4143-9245-f5b8d26218a1":{"text":"85","question":"f91d440a-c9c9-48af-ad83-cd0313d6dcac","isCorrect":false},"eef34541-639e-4c4f-baf8-eb614ed2c801":{"text":"Argentina","question":"7b90ec1d-8160-40af-b4d0-a7143eae871a","isCorrect":true},"124efb53-d5a2-47e5-be25-4990aa6ff5ef":{"text":"Colombia","question":"7b90ec1d-8160-40af-b4d0-a7143eae871a","isCorrect":false},"efe85292-3f1f-4320-9d5c-8b150da3845b":{"text":"Peru","question":"7b90ec1d-8160-40af-b4d0-a7143eae871a","isCorrect":false},"da805a44-a56b-40b9-820d-5b686da2644f":{"text":"Ecuador","question":"7b90ec1d-8160-40af-b4d0-a7143eae871a","isCorrect":false},"45974a0a-f1c7-4e80-9db6-4bbc1a11d0d6":{"text":"Greece","question":"0a2661b6-f439-4c5b-bcd3-a897b2d3758f","isCorrect":true},"bc66516d-339c-4026-a356-8332d6227fef":{"text":"Italy","question":"0a2661b6-f439-4c5b-bcd3-a897b2d3758f","isCorrect":false},"9bb1c93a-da8e-4d8d-96cc-22b2ac8a6cd3":{"text":"Bulgaria","question":"0a2661b6-f439-4c5b-bcd3-a897b2d3758f","isCorrect":false},"04d774b0-baba-4e25-a7f6-c14bccdbc48e":{"text":"Egypt","question":"0a2661b6-f439-4c5b-bcd3-a897b2d3758f","isCorrect":false},"231b2432-f36b-4a45-85db-b328c52cceac":{"text":"Hungary","question":"915acd46-68f5-4ea6-a1c5-d42c7fd6314b","isCorrect":true},"5f027bfc-0cb4-4669-9f1b-c1e9cfcdddf7":{"text":"Finland","question":"915acd46-68f5-4ea6-a1c5-d42c7fd6314b","isCorrect":false},"8435db60-ce2f-433c-8068-e08b4c16f3c2":{"text":"Poland","question":"915acd46-68f5-4ea6-a1c5-d42c7fd6314b","isCorrect":false},"41bc884f-92e6-4356-8aed-b18dcb5fef9a":{"text":"Austria","question":"915acd46-68f5-4ea6-a1c5-d42c7fd6314b","isCorrect":false},"e73e7674-af14-49a2-9565-25b4a593ca29":{"text":"Rin","question":"a7c191c9-88d0-44fa-a387-8c3b25476f90","isCorrect":true},"6000c8a1-dd20-4a09-af0f-bb9d2c26db59":{"text":"Don","question":"a7c191c9-88d0-44fa-a387-8c3b25476f90","isCorrect":false},"f77fc911-6fc1-43ff-82d1-7e62eafec0bf":{"text":"Ural","question":"a7c191c9-88d0-44fa-a387-8c3b25476f90","isCorrect":false},"b0862634-f730-41ee-a6d4-417dd7cbb853":{"text":"Pechora","question":"a7c191c9-88d0-44fa-a387-8c3b25476f90","isCorrect":false},"66ec01d6-8ee1-4f91-99a1-06fe17631e34":{"text":"Ecuador","question":"002e278f-ea15-434e-9738-592131ef584f","isCorrect":true},"730e8a3d-8ff1-4e53-a028-7906c31a4ec5":{"text":"Venezuela","question":"002e278f-ea15-434e-9738-592131ef584f","isCorrect":false},"490bcd18-2732-404c-864b-96aca81846b4":{"text":"Brazil","question":"002e278f-ea15-434e-9738-592131ef584f","isCorrect":false},"2e1dc389-2b0a-4d39-afda-a69aa9d5836f":{"text":"Bolivia","question":"002e278f-ea15-434e-9738-592131ef584f","isCorrect":false},"3598d381-fc45-45cd-81ac-409d8e3ff46f":{"text":"Waterloo","question":"3455e52d-9807-4366-8678-44a19b703438","isCorrect":true},"8c298138-06af-4a46-90e4-dd4db40f130e":{"text":"Austerlitz","question":"3455e52d-9807-4366-8678-44a19b703438","isCorrect":false},"976e805d-0fe6-400b-b287-d51a730acc42":{"text":"Boyaca","question":"3455e52d-9807-4366-8678-44a19b703438","isCorrect":false},"cd033400-25af-4ced-81c7-0d089fc82428":{"text":"Monterrey","question":"3455e52d-9807-4366-8678-44a19b703438","isCorrect":false},"bb3cca06-c0cd-4b9c-b8a7-3afb0cbdf80f":{"text":"George Washington","question":"5f7949bb-b877-46a6-8d1b-bf386e1fb852","isCorrect":true},"62178feb-2b6a-4289-a0c6-10e1c013ca80":{"text":"James Madison","question":"5f7949bb-b877-46a6-8d1b-bf386e1fb852","isCorrect":false},"2e5ac97e-ec2a-45fe-a76d-86fe475e1b47":{"text":"John Adams","question":"5f7949bb-b877-46a6-8d1b-bf386e1fb852","isCorrect":false},"6ddc619f-14c3-49d8-8248-77c9f30e84ff":{"text":"Thomas Jefferson","question":"5f7949bb-b877-46a6-8d1b-bf386e1fb852","isCorrect":false},"4c25902d-012b-410a-b81a-95b2ec368b9b":{"text":"Tiberio","question":"ec44da34-7745-4724-92a7-bc9993e7cb2c","isCorrect":true},"4b362623-ed2f-4072-a63b-cdb2e6994e53":{"text":"Trajano","question":"ec44da34-7745-4724-92a7-bc9993e7cb2c","isCorrect":false},"b46a7bba-0e87-45ed-a702-06c8e2da60e6":{"text":"Nerón","question":"ec44da34-7745-4724-92a7-bc9993e7cb2c","isCorrect":false},"d3b6b3f2-e4f0-4774-b8ff-6dbe88002705":{"text":"Marco Aurelio","question":"ec44da34-7745-4724-92a7-bc9993e7cb2c","isCorrect":false},"aed68915-7f2c-4709-b1c8-d85a18ab31ad":{"text":"Liberia","question":"fa00856c-4127-41c8-8338-e7abb9a740bf","isCorrect":true},"8a7b0e3f-3b72-48d0-80e5-20ac0f649a1c":{"text":"Zambia","question":"fa00856c-4127-41c8-8338-e7abb9a740bf","isCorrect":false},"ce37cdc5-feb6-4935-8e9d-db0a668667dc":{"text":"Tunisia","question":"fa00856c-4127-41c8-8338-e7abb9a740bf","isCorrect":false},"d7c07d79-2753-4400-b25f-2031af2e7157":{"text":"Sudan","question":"fa00856c-4127-41c8-8338-e7abb9a740bf","isCorrect":false},"49e2172e-e574-48ac-bc0f-3ec73c1b9304":{"text":"France","question":"73fb2f0b-7367-437b-8d58-a0d81fe1eee3","isCorrect":true},"ef297737-fd71-49bd-80bb-d1bfd4da2f21":{"text":"Argeria","question":"73fb2f0b-7367-437b-8d58-a0d81fe1eee3","isCorrect":false},"10a6864c-120f-4170-85fe-20cd1a26d640":{"text":"Libya","question":"73fb2f0b-7367-437b-8d58-a0d81fe1eee3","isCorrect":false},"2e98ff45-69db-4bcf-9742-012b5697e033":{"text":"Belgium","question":"73fb2f0b-7367-437b-8d58-a0d81fe1eee3","isCorrect":false}}